

Telephone 619 300 9004

Email cacananta@gmail.com

Website www.coreycodes.io

GitHub github.com/Cacananta

LinkedIn.com /in/cacananta/

# **Projects**

Delicious Deliveries

During this team project we created a full-stack food delivery application. We used React Redux to manage our components, we built database endpoints to capture user authentication, and used an agile work flow to manage our one-week sprint.

### California Surf Report

This surf report app uses React and Express to help get the latest surf conditions. Although the initial build only took me 72 hours, this is an ongoing project that I hope to launch as a Google PWA (progressive web application). Stay tuned!

### JobLeads

We created a job aggregator application to help Origin Code Academy graduates with job searches. I worked as a back-end developer building database tables and sending API endpoint data to our client interface. Our four-person team is very excited our application will help future Origin students.

## What I can do

Javascript Developer with excellent communication and presentation skills. Quick learner with natural analytical skills and fast growing technical knowledge. I enjoy the process of taking something difficult or seemingly impossible and turning it into a reality.

Skills	Proficiency	Appeal
JavaScript	• • • •	• • • •
HTML/CSS	• • • •	• • • • •
React.js	• • • •	• • • • •
Node.js	• • • •	• • • •
Redux.js	• • • •	• • • •
MongoDB	• • • •	• • • •

# **Experience**

LPL Financial 2008-2017

Associate Analyst

2014-2017

- Raised Infrastructure team efficiency by 25% by streamlining processes
- Saved Dividend team 0.25 FTE by creating data scrubbing procedure
- Completed and passed 100% of quarterly internal audit reviews.
- Tested enhancement system that led to reduction of five offshore FTEs

### Compliance Analyst

2013-2014

- Met quarterly quota to resolve 90% of high-risk flags reducing firm risk
- Surveilled \$250 million of assets on a quarterly basis
- Conducted surveillance to ensure compliance with SEC and EINIRA

## Education

### Origin Code Academy

2017

### FULL STACK(MERN) JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPMENT

• I learned full-stack JavaScript development best practices with React.js, Redux.js, ¡Query, HTML/CSS, Node.js, MongoDB, SQL, and more

### San Diego State University

2002 - 2007

#### BACHELORS OF ARTS. INTERNATIONAL ECONOMICS

• I learned the ins and outs of global commerce and how fiscal and social decisions influence the standard of living across the world